Hey Malik, first of all,
>> how you doing?
>> Doing good. First of all,
congratulations. Welcome to Las Vegas.
My question for you just how do you
vision your role in the next level? Uh,
you know, you play for a ton of speed
and also you um you play with a ton of
speed and you also are quality on
special you, excuse me, provide quality
support on special teams. So, what do
you envision your role to be here with
the Raiders? man, what I vision my role
to be, you know, man, just coming in
just do whatever they need me to do.
Whether, you know, that's coming in be
the deep threat, whether that's coming
in, you know, you know, be a special
teams guy, you know, just doing whatever
I can to put the team in the best light.
>> Hey, Malik, uh, welcome to Las Vegas.
Um, you're entering a team that just
took Fernando Mendoza with the number
one overall pick. I know you played
against him this year, um, with Oregon
and Indiana. I just want to know any
impressions you have of him or any
memories that you know of that game um
just watching him.
>> Yeah. So, man, you know, the memories I
let them go out the out the window, you
know, once the game ended, but no, you
know, I was able to, you know, speak
with him for a little bit at the combine
and, you know, just me being able to
talk to him for that 10, 15 minutes, you
know, I just realized how how humble he
is, bro. And it's just like, you know,
he obviously he works, you know, super
hard, but past football, you know, he's
just a great person. You know, that's
just I can't wait to be, you know,
alongside teammates with some guy that,
you know, with a guy like that. So, it's
going to be super exciting. You know,
it's going to be super fun. You know, I
can't wait. You know, obviously, he got
the he got the best of the best of
Oregon, you know, those two times, but
shoot, you know, we're going to be able
to put those aside and we're going to be
able to, you know, have an electric year
this coming up year.
>> Yeah.
Hi, Levi Damian from USA Today. I know
you um you you started out at Alabama or
a community college, Alabama, Florida
State. So, you moved around each year.
What would you say that you found at
Oregon um to have the breakout season
that you did,
>> man? I just feel like at Oregon I was
playing with super confidence and shoot,
when you're out there with super
confidence, I feel like nobody could
stop me. You know, just being able to
carry that mindset over to this next
level, man, it's going to be super fun
to show what I can do.
that they began.
>> I I was reading about um you know your
youth and and not being able to get into
football. Part of it obviously uh you
know it's kind of expensive to even
enter into the sport. Um what what does
it feel like now to to reach this point
to make it to the NFL?
>> Man, it's it's a blessing, man. Just
knowing, you know, God is amazing. Just
knowing that he wouldn't put no task in
front of my face that I'm not able to
handle. So just knowing that, you know,
I started so young to see that, you
know, this dream that I had since I was
12 years old. Obviously, I didn't get to
start playing till my sophomore year,
but to know that hearing my name called
today, man, it was just nothing but a
blessing and it was just, you know, a
very cool experience to be able to, you
know, celebrate with my fans, my friends
and family.
>> How much pride will you take in showing
at the next level? You know, some of the
scouts that, you know, maybe had some
negatives on you were not the full
router, uh, you know, deep ball guy. How
excited are you to be able to show maybe
you can do everything at the wide
receiver? man, I know I'm coming to a
system that's going to allow me to
perform. And so just whatever they ask
me to do, I'm going to come out there
and do it with my best ability. And you
know, coming up the next couple years,
you know, I'm'll be able to put that
stamp and show people who Malik Benson
is. So it's going to be super fun.
>> Hey Malik, kind of playing off of that a
little bit like in some of your scouting
reports and they talk about your, you
know, ability to go over the middle and
the fact that, you know, you're not
afraid to go over the middle and catch
those balls. I guess in a system that
has a lot of West Coast principles and
stuff like that, how much do you think
you can shine and kind of show that area
of your game? question.
>> Yeah, man. Just knowing that, you know,
they picked me, so they're going to, you
know, ask me to come and do a lot of
things and I just know that my
preparation is going to take over. So,
no matter what they ask me to do, I'm
going be 100% confident with my task
because I'm going to spend a lot of time
off the field being able to, you know,
understand my spots and understand the
offense and having a guy, you know, what
better way to have a guy like, you know,
Mendoza, a guy that's come in. So, we're
going to be learning the offense at the
same time. So, man, you know, we just
got to we just got to get in the
playbook early and I feel like, you
know, me and him were going to be
lethal.
Hey Malik, what do what do you know
about the Raiders as an organization?
The tradition, the history, everything
like that as you come in,
>> man. So, it's crazy one thing, you know,
I'm from Kansas City, so you know,
growing up growing up, you know, I
always, you know, had my hate for the
Raiders, but to finally be on the on the
side to where, you know, it's us versus
anybody and us against the world, man, I
love it, man. just just knowing the
history, you know, I'm just glad that
I'm able to come in and just make my
mark and, you know, just be a part of,
you know, this great tradition and, you
know, be a part, you know, we're going
to turn this thing into the right
direction and do what we need to do. So,
you know, that confetti's falling, the
banner is rising at the end of the year.
>> Speaking of the confetti and the banner,
you're in Eugene, but uh a little kind
of close to you with Seattle and that
that offense is kind of coming here with
with coach Kubak. Did you pay any any
mind to what Seattle was doing on their
Super Bowl run last year, or were you
just totally focused in on what you were
doing,
>> man? And so yeah, you know, Seattle was
one of the teams that, you know, I like
to watch a lot just seeing, you know,
motions, how they use the receivers and
just, you know, just their plays and I
feel like, you know, they had they had
really good plays. Just being able to
watch them and, you know, shoot, getting
a guy like me in this offense with, you
know, us being able to do that, it's
going to be super exciting just to be
able to show that I can obviously go
deep, but, you know, I can run every
single route, you know, go around the
the middle and do whatever it takes for
this offense. And I'm, you know, I'm
just super excited, super blessed for
this opportunity.
>> Thank you. Congrats again.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> Thanks so much, Malik. appreciate it.
>> Thank you.